Hello everyone. I am Ana Imamoto of Equal Love and
I'm Maonko Uesawa, the new Equal Me.
Yay!
This is the first time for the two of us to appear on the Equinojoy Channel as a project like this!
I am the leader of the group. Hello, I'm Maonko Uesawa.
We are the Leaders. We look forward to working with you.
Hello, I'm Iconojoy.
So, today we are here at the Icono Joy Costume Exhibition!
Wow!
Yay!
Isn't it cute already?
It's so cute!
It's wonderful!
It's on a hanger.
Yes, it's on a hanger.
Maenko, what month is it today?
Yes, today is the 5th of January!
It's 5!
It's the 5th.
It's the day before the Icono Joy Costume Exhibition starts.
Yes, that's right.
We would like to have a special two-person exhibition,
I know there are some of you who can't come,
We would like to share the charm of this exhibition with as many people as possible!
So, let's go!
Let's go!
Dakidaki dakidaki dakidaki!
I'm nervous I'm excited I'm having so much fun
Can I go now?
I'm already looking. I'm already looking.
Wow!
Oh, my God, I miss it!
It brings back memories!
Are you sure it's okay to look so close?
Actually, you're not supposed to touch them.
But I'm a member, so please forgive me.
Moeiko too.
Moeiko, but I can't touch you.
It's kind of fresh.
Hey! Long time no see! You look good! This outfit!
So this is Hitomi's costume.
Hitomi, is that you? How have you been?
It's been a long time!
We haven't seen each other in a long time.
We've been in the sea and in the mountains with this.
It's an old costume.
I've seen it many times in music videos.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I've never seen it this close before.
I'm so happy! I was also curious about this one.
The process of costume making
We don't know anything about this kind of thing.
Study Request
Nudity Direction
The design
Design decision
Gathering fabrics is amazing, isn't it?
Making one with a provisional seam
He made one tentative stitch.
Revisions. Variations.
Amazing!
Temporary sewing Hair ornament
The hair ornaments are so cute every time.
Yes, they are.
They match the outfits
to match the outfits.
We love this day!
We love it too!
We love the fittings.
I love it when fittings are on the schedule.
I get so excited.
Yes, we are.
I'm so glad.
Thank you for everything.
Really nice, cute outfits.
I'm so happy.
How many do you have? Do you want to see?
I asked you how many I have.
There are only three so far.I've only worn three so far.
He eats so much!
They say there are 188.
Wait, there's that many? Wait, wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait. 188 pieces? That's amazing!
We're in dreamland!
We've got to go. We'll never make it in time.
Wait, Anna's...
Anna Anna Anna Anna Anna Anna Anna Anna Anna
This is Anna.
Anna's white coat.
How are you?
So cute!
And this outfit... the equal love is hidden here...
Yes, it is.
The hat is so cute.
There are all kinds of decorations.
Each member has a slightly different one.
Each one has a message or comment like this.
The ribbons can be removed for future use.
You can take off the ribbon and use it in the future.
It's wonderful!
We can't go on at all!
I'll be here for another hour or so.
I'm with you.
I miss it.
This is like Sanna's.
The sleeves were taken off once for the summer version.
But we wanted to wear the long-sleeved version again.
they put them back on again.
I miss it.
Because one-too-many
You gave me the wrong one.
I'm sorry.
I missed you, Wangchun.
I missed you.
Thank you for your help.
Thank you.
I love your outfit.
That's great.
I'm so glad they're all lined up!
I think we were probably in the one-too-one-too
during the audition period.
the costumes that the collaborators wore during the audition period.
It's really one of a kind.
It's a lot of detail in each one of them.
I was looking at the close-up pictures like this.
It was amazing.
So many of them.
Subliminal.
It was so emo.
You can really see them up close.
I can't believe I got to see it.
Oh, my God!
I'm so happy.
Big Lili and Zulu Zulu
All the singles!
That's great!
Mr. Shokori!
Shokori-san.
It's really amazing how fast you change.
I put it on my TikTok.
Please check it out!
I've seen it.
Please do.
And the stolons.
This is...
It's the brothers' version.
And this is the version that he made for the music station.
Mr. Ito of Yoani, who made this for us when we were on the music station.
from Mr. Ito of Yoani.
That's right.
We were
fitting.
I thought it was a different fitting.
But then he said...
I was told it was the costume for the M-star show.
It's one of my favorite outfits.
I love it.
Shall we continue?Shall we continue?
Wow.
So many...
There's a human being.
Mannequins.
I didn't know mannequins existed in the world.
Yes, they do.
All the mannequins are rushing here.
They say it's going to be another day.
This is a cameo.
Wow!
All the members are here.
Wow, really.
Look at the view.
I'm so happy.
It's a dream come true.
I've never been to a costume show.
There's so many of them.
Everything was really cute.
All the singles
I haven't seen this outfit in a long time.
It was the first time I saw it in person.
What's more
I've never seen these outfits in person before.
I don't know...
It's like they have a certain vibe to them.
or have a certain image of them.
I think it's love.
Then, let's continue.
Oh, there's Shukipi, too.
I miss it.
So cute!
The black pink is amazing.
It's really something.
You can tell when you see it on the side.
Surprising.
Have you ever seen it this close up?
No.
And now...
I've missed this one.
Wow, there's a lot of accessories.
There are accessories, too.
This one is lovely, too.
Combined with the cuteness of Ms. Ikolove
combined with the cuteness of Ms. Ikolove.
There's more!
There's more?
Wait.
It's Anna.
Hi.
I haven't seen you in a while.
First time in person.
It's been a while.
Look at this... there's a member in navy blue and another in a white hat.
There are members in navy blue and white hats.
And the "Toys 'n' Girls" coupling song.
You've got a great lineup here, don't you?
I love the costumes.
They're great.
I think Aiko's here, too.
It's been a while.
Finally!
I'm in my Ikko costume.
I've missed this one too.
Wow!
This is amazing.
It's not really amazing.
It really is.
I can't believe there's all this stuff.
memories for each live performance.
We had the chance to see it.
We have memories of seeing them and watching them on film.
And all of them are here now.
It's all condensed here.
It's amazing!
I'm so happy.
You know what?
It's definitely the Shokorisa set.
They're all Shokorisa sets.
It's so cute!
The back is cute, too.The back is cute, too.
Butterfly Fairy
I'm glad you have the recipe.
That's great.
It's so cute.
It's really cute.
It's amazing how good it looks on you.
It's sparkly and matching.
So cute.
Mike, this looks really good on you, too.
Costume.
Oh my God, this brings back memories.
Like Budokan.
I cried the moment they changed the costume.
I cried.
It's not fair.
Sachihara-san said it would be more beautiful if I raised it up.
"You look better with it up.
She told me it would be more beautiful if I raised it higher.
We all practiced taking it and raising it up.
We all practiced hard.
At first it was a little bit
It was a little hard to do at first.
But the costume designer made it easier.
to make it easier to do.
I didn't know there was such a behind-the-scenes story.
Come on, come on...
It's time to go.
I've come to the light blue world!
This is Moemi!
Amazing!
Always, always...
Thank you very much.
Hello everyone, Moe-mi!
It's been a long time since I've seen this.
Handwritten
It's Nacchan!
This is amazing.
It's our first time.
That's the outfit you wore for your debut.
It's so cute! Look, look, look!
It's real.
This is your summer dress.
It's embroidered on the sailor back.
It's more equal.
It's amazing... that our costumes are being displayed like this.
It's so strange to see our costumes on display like this.
It's a strange feeling, isn't it?
Uniforms look good on you, don't they, Moemi?
That makes me happy.
But really, really...
The memories of your sweat, tears and smiles
It brings back memories.
You really have a lot of memories in your uniform.
It's full of memories, isn't it?
I wish you could see it up close.
Choco Mela
Chocolatieri chocolatieri chocolatieri chocolatieri chocolatieri chocolatieri chocolatieri.
Yes.
Thank you for your help.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Choco Mela is like a chocolate assortment
I don't know...
There are so many kinds of browns.
And they chose the color to match the members.
It's my favorite costume.
Great costumes!
PIC.
I'm here.
PIC, it's mine.
It's too cool, really.
No, it's not.
The pic outfit is amazing.
I feel so strong when I wear it.
I wish I could wear it all the time.
I want to walk around in it every day.
Every day.
It's cute.
So cute.Cute.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Breathe.
It's so up-to-date.
It's all here.
This place is even better than I thought it would be.
I'm impressed.
There's even a Sparkle!
Ultra rare kisses and the latest
The latest and greatest!
And both of them have the same Samachoko!
Twins!
It's a stage!
Samacho Doremi's
This is the costume they wore when they were onstage with Samacho Doremi.
These are the costumes we wore for the role of Samachodoremi.
They chose the colors and stuff.
They chose the colors and made it for me.
It's hard to say.
Some of the members wore colors they usually don't wear
It was fresh and new.
It was fresh.
You know, when I look at it like this, I think it's kind of tiny.
What's that? Huh?
It's so tiny.
Is this Kirari?
Oh, Kirari, it's so tiny.
They're going to take it away.
Next is the yellow zone.
Maybe this is the yellow zone.
Here we are in the Nearly Called Joy zone!
Hello, Joy!
Hello there.
A very lonely lion.
I'm always in uniform.
I think it looks like a tie.
Or a jacket.
I think it's more in keeping with the character.
Styled to fit each character.
It's a highlight.
We've seen Joy in a music video for the first time.
It's the first time we've seen her in a music video.
as we look at the outfits of each of them.
I'm sure
I can see the image of this girl
I can see it.
And
Nearly Call Joy
It's the kind of outfit you'd expect from Nearly Coal Joy.
But the checks and stripes
I've never seen it this close before.
I don't know if I'm allowed to get this close for the first time.
Thank you very much for your help.
Thank you very much.
But it's amazing.
Amazing!
This way?
This way.
Icono Joy.
Oh, my God.
This is Icono Joy's corner.
Wow!
They're wearing the costumes from Iconoi24Girls.
It's been a long time.
But I'm really impressed with this outfit of Ms. Ikolag.
It's pinkish, but...
But purplish.
and the image of the gorgeous color
and Noemi's
emerald green-ish image of Noemi
the image of emerald green
I loved each color
I loved it.
For Ikonoijoy, the pants style
very unusual pants style
isn't it?
Each one is pinkEach one is pink.
light blue and yellow.
Each has its own points of interest.
And they have different shapes.
It's a highlight.
I hope you can see what each of them looks like.
I hope you can see what the stamped surface looks like.
Oh, it's gorgeous!
Oh, it's so sparkly!
Oh, my gosh!
Each of the iconoijoys
Mixed with each other.
So colorful!
The shape of the sleeves, the length of the skirt
the length of the skirt, the number of frills
and the number of frills.
It's like this one over here.
Some of the members have stats
and the ones in the middle.
There are two kinds.
The one that Joy was wearing...
Equal Love and Noemie wore the same skirt.
The skirt that Joy was wearing
I see that they have inherited it.
Well, let's go.
Bye bye.
Wait, Emozone!
I'm wearing an Emozone.
That's so emo.
It's been a while.
You guys have grown up.
You've all grown up.
Have you grown?
I hope you'll continue to grow
I hope you will continue to grow.
Triple date.
We're here now, aren't we?
It's been a long time.
It's so emo when you come in at the end.
It's nice.
And there's a screen.
That's for sure.
Is the music video playing?
Like an introduction video.
One group at a time.
It makes you want to stop, doesn't it?
I probably would.
If there wasn't a time limit.
I'd be winding up for a year.
I'm winding up now.
That's not enough time.
It's not enough.
Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait.
Here it comes.
They're here.
Oh, my God.
I've never seen this before.
This is...
Could this be...
This is a photo booth costume for fans to wear
This is a photo booth costume for fans to wear.
They went to the trouble of making a new one!
You can put it in now!
It's amazing!
There it is!
Peek-a-boo!
What's that?
Oh, my God.
It's a communications table, isn't it?
Why am I set up so small?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Huh? Huh?
Was that the radio tower?
Yeah, it's the same.
It's the same one.
Oh!
Do you want to wear it, Moeko?
Want to try it on? Want to take a picture?
I'm representing my fans.On behalf of our fans, we would like to thank you for allowing us to wear it.
I am going to put on our favorite Shinobu-san!
Shinobu-san.
Thank you very much for letting Moeko-chan come.
I'm sorry, I'm wearing it.
Wow! Wow!
You're in the middle of the room.
I'll take your picture.
Wow! You're so cute.
Can I look in the mirror, too? Sure.
Oh, wow.
You're so cute! You don't mind, do you?
I'd love to be your equal.
Huh! Excuse me.
That's funny. Excuse me.
He's bowing.
Now let me take your picture.
I don't know.
Do you have any advice on what kind of pose I should do?
It's like a poi. It's like a flow.
Same pose.
A little more this way, over there.
A little more this way. There.
There it is.
Here we go. Cheese.
A little more this way.
A little too far. Sorry. Sorry.
Cheese!
Here we go.
Okay, look.
I tried the same pose.
Wow! Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God!
This is amazing!
This is like a dream! I think it's a dream!
I mean, this is made of the same fabric as Equalab's!
And I hear this place is absolutely gorgeous!
I'll have to enjoy it more before I wear it.
Wow!
I want to wear it with you.
I'll wear it too.
I think I'll wear an S.
Oh, wow! It's so solid.
It's so solid.
Cute.
Hello everyone, this is Equal Love.
Yay!
Thank you so much.
Wow, that's great!
I still want you to take a picture of me on stage.
Huh?
Huh? I'm losing my hair.
I want to wear it home.
Do you want it at home?
I want it for my house.
I really want to live here.
I want to live here.
Would you take a picture with me?
Please take a picture with us.
Please.
Do you want me to go here? Where do you want to go?
I think I'll go here.
Just one more in the middle.
I'll go here.
I'll do the same pose.
Thank you very much.
No, this really makes me feel like I'm used to being your favorite equalizer,
Yay!
It's a great happy space.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for creating a really wonderful space.
It's wonderful.
The last one.
The last one? I don't know.
Tears!
Maggie Maggie
This is Natan's costume exhibition.
Nagisa is packed.The beach is packed.
I was really nostalgic for songs like "Arrived, Love You".
Nagisa was just born at that time.
It really brings back memories.
I can't count the number of times I've seen the music video and had my heart shot out of my chest.
But this one of Nagisa, I feel like she's grown up.
It's so wonderful.
It's wonderful.
It makes me cry.
I think the skirts are all the same,
But the top one is for each of us.
Memories.
I'm so deeply moved.
I really am.
I hope that everyone will remember these memories for a long time to come.
It may already be over. Maybe it's already over.
Even if you can't make it, please take a look at this video.
That's all I have to say.
Thank you very much.
I want to do this again and again.
Let's go there at the end.
Well, that's it, we've finished our tour.
It was a great time.
It was too good.
I was surprised to see so many costumes,
There are always names on the hangers and stuff,
I was so happy every time,
Every single one of them has a story or a memory,
I feel so happy that fans can see them,
I hope I can continue to wear these wonderful costumes in the future,
I hope that everyone at Ikonoijoy will do their best so that I can continue to wear these wonderful costumes.
Thank you very much for this wonderful project.
Not only in Tokyo,
I wish we could do this kind of thing again in various places.
I am sure you are right.
I wish so many people in Japan could see it,
I wish many people in Japan could see the costumes,
Please take a look at this video.
Please take a look at this video as well.
So, everyone, please continue to support Icono Joy.
Thank you very much.
Now I would like to write Anne at the end.
I'll write this one first.
Then we decided to write more and more here, so I'm going to write it.
Here I go!
Let's go!
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle!
Love
Yama
Moto
Unna
Yooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Woohoo!
Yes, I wrote it!
I wrote it!
One more then.
Yes, I'd like to write one too
Oh, I'm sorry.
Then I'll write
I'll write here in Taisho.
I will write in the Taisho place
Teiran
Yo!
Mee
Mi-Mi again!
The happiest space in the world! Nice!
Yes! So I'm done signing autographs!